[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORT]
This is my little
brother George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is the day
of the school fete.
Miss Rabbit
is running the raffle.
Roll up! Roll up!
The top prize is a ride
in my hot air balloon.
Wow, that sounds fun.
[BARKS]
Can I have a ticket, please?
The blue ticket wins...
a toy car.
Well done, Danny.
Can I have a ticket, please?
Thank you, Peppa.
What are you hoping to win?
The balloon ride.
Wouldn't it be nicer to win
the homemade chocolate cake?
Daddy Pig loves
homemade chocolate cake.
[GIGGLES]
The red ticket wins...
the balloon ride!
ALL:
Hooray!
All aboard
for the balloon ride.
How many passengers,
please?
Four, please.
And Teddy.
Dinosaur.
Oh, and a teddy
and a dinosaur.
That makes six.
All aboard.
[GIGGLING]
Hurry up, Daddy Pig.
Hop aboard.
Quick, Daddy.
Splice the main brace.
Chocks away.
Full steam ahead.
Very impressive,
Miss Rabbit.
You must be
an expert pilot.
Not really.
This the first time
I've ever flown a balloon.
Oh.
Hold tight.
Miss Rabbit heats up the air
in the balloon
to make it rise
into the sky.
Bye-bye.
ALL:
Bye-bye!
Would anyone like
to do the map reading?
I will.
Are you sure, Daddy Pig?
[SNORTS]
I'm very good
at map reading.
Oh. This map
is a bit difficult.
[ALL LAUGH]
Shall we go higher?
Yes, please.
Higher. Higher.
The balloon is rising high
into the sky.
Oh, where did
the sky go?
DADDY PIG:
Don't worry, Peppa.
We're just flying
through a cloud.
GEORGE AND PEPPA:
Ooh!
Wow. The sky is back again.
ALL:
Hooray!
[GIGGLES]
♪ Big balloon, big balloon ♪
♪ Bigger than the sun
And moon ♪
♪ Flying high in the sky ♪
♪ Fly and fly
And fly and fly ♪
[ALL LAUGH]
Look, Teddy,
we're flying really high.
Peppa, be careful
you don't drop--
Teddy!
I've dropped Teddy.
[MOMMY PIG GASPS]
DADDY PIG: Ooh.
Don't worry, Peppa.
We'll rescue Teddy.
Hold tight, everybody.
We're going down.
Miss Rabbit
is making the balloon go down
so that Teddy can be rescued.
DADDY PIG:
I can't see Teddy anywhere.
There he is.
Teddy's caught in a tree.
I can use this anchor
to rescue Teddy.
Slowly, slowly. There.
Daddy Pig
has rescued Teddy.
Teddy.
ALL: Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
Oh, dear. No one is looking
where they are going.
Look out!
Tree straight ahead!
Hold tight.
Ooh.
PEPPA:
First Teddy was stuck in a tree,
and now we are stuck
in a tree.
Daddy Pig, do you know
where we are?
Uh...
We're lost, aren't we?
Yes.
Oh.
Ooh.
Look, everyone.
That's Granny
and Grandpa's house.
Yes. We must be
in Grandpa Pig's garden.
As I thought.
Ahoy there, Granny Pig
and Grandpa Pig!
Goodness me.
Ahoy there, Miss Rabbit!
Uh, help. Please.
Grandpa,
we can't get down!
Don't worry.
I've got a ladder.
ALL:
Hooray!
Everyone climbs down
from the big balloon.
Granny, Grandpa!
Miss Rabbit took us
for a ride
in her big balloon.
How very exciting.
I'm afraid the most
exciting thing we can offer
is a piece of my homemade
chocolate cake.
Homemade chocolate cake.
That is exciting.
[GIGGLES]
That was the best
balloon ride ever.
Mmm. And that was
the best chocolate cake ever.
[CHUCKLES]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today is George's birthday.
[ROOSTER CROWS]
It is very early
in the morning.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLING]
George,
it's too early.
Dinosaur. Grrr.
Go back to bed.
[GIGGLES]
It sounds like someone's
up bright and early.
[SNORTS]
BOTH:
Happy Birthday, George.
George woke me up.
You woke everyone up
on your birthday, Peppa.
That was different.
That was my birthday.
And today is
George's birthday.
[YAWNS]
Happy Birthday,
George.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
Here's your present,
George.
[SNORTS]
[RATTLES]
Ooh.
[SNORTS]
Dinosaur!
[GIGGLES]
I knew it would be
some sort of dinosaur thingy.
Grrr.
[CHUCKLES]
Squeeze its tummy.
[TOY ROARS]
Eek!
Too scary.
[ALL LAUGH]
George, I've made you
a birthday card.
Can you guess
what the picture is?
George cannot guess.
I was going
to paint you a flower.
Oh.
George does not like flowers.
But in the end,
I painted you a...
Dinosaur!
That's a lovely
picture, Peppa.
Yes. I'm very good
at painting.
Now we're going
somewhere very special
for George's
birthday treat.
Yippee! Let's go.
Where are we going?
[SNORTS]
You'll see.
[GEORGE GIGGLES]
The family are setting off
for George's birthday treat.
[HORN BEEPS]
Are we going
to the circus?
No, but it's somewhere
just as good.
Um, is it the cinema?
DADDY PIG:
No. Much better.
I just can't guess.
Where can they be going?
DADDY PIG:
We're here!
The family have arrived
at the museum.
Why are we
at the museum?
Come on, you'll see.
What can George's
birthday treat be?
George, what do you like best
in the whole world?
Dinosaur.
[GIGGLES]
Ooh, dinosaur.
George's birthday treat
is a visit
to the museum dinosaur room.
Huh. Silly old
dinosaurs again.
[GIGGLING]
Dinosaur.
[BEEPS]
[ROARS]
[GASPS]
[CRIES]
Don't be frightened,
George.
It's not
a real dinosaur.
It's just a robot.
Look, I stand
on this spot and...
[BEEPS]
[ROARS]
[GIGGLES]
[BEEPS]
[ROARS]
[GIGGLES]
Grrr!
[ALL LAUGH]
And now there's another
surprise.
All of George and Peppa's
friends are here.
ALL:
Surprise!
Mommy Rabbit has made
a birthday cake for George.
Can anyone guess
what sort cake it is?
A dinosaur cake?
It is!
What an amazing guess, Peppa.
ALL:
Happy Birthday, George!
[GIGGLES]
There's one last surprise.
Follow me.
What is the last surprise?
What do you think it is,
Peppa.
It's probably something
to do with dinosaurs.
Oh. What's that?
[LAUGHS]
It just needs
to be filled with air.
I know, I know.
It's a bouncy castle.
Peppa loves bouncy castles.
But if it's for George,
why isn't it something
to do with dinosaurs?
Ho-ho!
It is a dinosaur.
A bouncy dinosaur.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGHING]
George loves
bouncy dinosaurs.
Everyone loves
This is great.
Happy birthday, George.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Suzy Sheep has come
to play with Peppa.
[BLEATS AND LAUGHS]
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, Suzy.
This is my new friend,
Leo Lion.
Where is he?
There's no one there.
Suzy has made up
a pretend friend.
Can't you see him, Peppa?
Um...
[GIGGLES]
Let's play catch.
Okay. To you, Leo.
Peppa throws the ball
to Suzy's pretend friend.
Leo can't catch the ball.
He can. He just doesn't
like playing catch.
What does Leo
like doing?
He likes to roar.
Is he going to roar now?
Um, yes. Ahem.
Roar.
Wasn't that you?
No, that was Leo.
Ah. Hello, Leo.
Peppa pretends
that she can see Leo Lion.
Leo, will you be
my friend too?
[WHISPERS]
What did he say?
He's nodding his head.
That means yes.
Peppa, Suzy,
would you like to come inside
and have some fruit cake?
Mommy Pig has two slices of
fruit cake for Suzy and Peppa.
Mommy, Suzy's got
a pretend friend.
He's called Leo Lion.
I see. And does he
like fruit cake too?
Roar!
Leo loves fruit cake.
Don't be silly, Peppa.
That wasn't Leo,
that was you.
Leo prefers
chocolate cake.
I haven't got chocolate cake.
Will Leo have some fruit cake?
Roar. He will try
a little slice.
Mommy Pig gives some cake
to Suzy's pretend friend.
George is playing
with Mr. Dinosaur.
Dinosaur. Grrr.
George, you're sitting
on Leo.
George does not know that Suzy
has made up a friend.
Roar!
[CRIES]
Um, Leo Lion says
he can't finish his cake,
so George can have it.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
[GIGGLES]
Can we play upstairs now?
Yes. Let's play
dressing up.
I was asking Leo.
Oh.
Roar!
Leo says he likes
playing dressing up.
Good.
Come on, Leo.
Peppa and Suzy
are playing dressing up.
Peppa is going
to be a fairy.
I grant you one wish.
My wish is
to be Queen Suzy.
And Leo Lion
will be the jester.
He doesn't want
to be the jester.
He wants to be the king.
Here is Daddy Pig.
Mommy Pig tells me
you have a very special visitor.
It's only Suzy,
Daddy.
Are you sure there isn't
someone else, Peppa?
There is someone else:
King Leo Lion.
Roar!
[CHUCKLES]
It's an honor
to meet you, King Leo.
Daddy Pig pretends
he can see King Leo.
May I say what a fine
golden mane you have?
Yes, it is very fine.
And he is wearing
his best red trousers.
Oh, yes.
And his blue jumper.
Silly Peppa. Leo isn't
wearing a blue jumper.
He's wearing
his best green shirt.
Well, it is sort
of a bluey-green.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Peppa, Suzy,
your friends are here.
Peppa's friends are here.
They are all wearing
their boots.
Let's jump
in muddy puddles.
BOTH:
Yes!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Are you sure
Leo should jump in puddles
without his boots?
Oh, I forgot.
Leo's wearing his boots
as well.
[LAUGHS]
Look at Leo.
He's jumping
up and down too.
Roar!
Everyone loves jumping
up and down in muddy puddles,
even pretend friends.
Roar!
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are painting today.
We need some old newspaper
to put on the table.
Yes.
[SNORTS]
Daddy Pig is reading
his newspaper.
You can have
my newspaper
when I've finished
reading it.
All right,
here you are, George.
Hooray!
Now we can start
painting.
Silly George.
Big children do not put
their hands in the paint.
[GIGGLES]
George loves painting
with his hands.
[LAUGHS]
Peppa loves painting
with her hands.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Very good.
Can I have a potato,
Mommy Pig?
They aren't cooked yet,
Daddy Pig.
Are you hungry,
Daddy?
I'm not going to eat it.
Watch this.
What is Daddy Pig doing?
BOTH:
Ooh.
Now, who can tell me
what this is?
A flower.
[ALL LAUGH]
Clever Daddy.
[CHUCKLES]
I loved painting
when I was a young piggy.
Now, where are
my old painting things?
[GIGGLES]
Daddy, why are you
wearing that funny hat?
[LAUGHS]
This is my beret.
It puts me in the mood
for painting pictures.
Now, what shall I paint?
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
Well chosen, George.
I'll paint
the old cherry tree.
What's that?
It's an easel, Peppa.
It holds my canvas.
What's a canvas?
It's a bit like paper,
for very special paintings.
Is that
toothpaste?
[LAUGHS]
No, Peppa.
These are special paints
for grown-up artists.
There. What color
shall we begin with?
Red, please.
Why red, Peppa?
Red is
my favorite color.
But first we need
to paint the sky.
Look. What color is it?
Blue of course
DADDY PIG:
Very good.
Let's start with blue.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Now for the cherry tree.
We need green
for the leaves.
PEPPA:
But there isn't any green.
DADDY PIG:
Never mind.
If we mix blue paint
with yellow paint,
we can make green.
Mixing blue and yellow
makes green.
GEORGE AND PEPPA:
Ooh.
What lovely
green leaves.
And here's some grass.
What about
the branches?
We haven't got
brown paint.
We can make brown.
We'll mix the green
and the red.
Mixing green and red
makes brown.
GEORGE AND PEPPA:
Ooh.
Daddy Pig paints the tree trunk
and the branches.
BOTH:
Wow.
[GIGGLES]
Daddy,
can I paint the cherries?
Yes, Peppa.
Put your finger in the paint
and dab it onto the tree.
[GIGGLES]
One... two... three.
DADDY PIG:
Well done.
Now it's
George's turn.
[GIGGLES]
What a great painter
you are, George.
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
There.
The painting is finished.
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
[QUACKING]
Oh, it's the ducks.
Hello, Mrs. Duck.
We're painting
a picture.
The ducks are running
through Daddy's paint.
Shoo! Shoo!
Naughty ducks.
Shoo, ducks!
Shoo!
Stay away
from our painting.
Whoa!
[QUACKING]
Oh, no, the ducks
have made paint footprints
all over the painting.
Oh, dear.
What was all that noise?
Mommy, the ducks
have spoiled our painting.
Hmm, let me see.
The ducks are making
paint footprints in the garden,
just like the ones
on the painting.
Daddy's painting
isn't spoiled, Peppa.
It's perfect.
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
Oh, yes.
I am a bit of an expert
at painting.
And so are the ducks.
[ALL QUACKING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]